Hey, just wanted to run you through the proposal real quick. Um,
a lot of it is just to be blunt, templated information.
You can kind of read through it on your own time.
A lot of it's what we already discussed. So again,
you can kind of breeze through these screens,
talk a little bit more about scope, results, et cetera.
I just wanted to run you through the proposed scope and price real quick.
So this would be on a monthly basis. Um,
we go month to month. Now we don't really do long-term contracts.
Just if you're not happy with this, then we had just choose to partner ways. So,
uh, just to run you through it real quick, um, you know,
essentially these are kind of like an average over like what a six month
campaign would be. Campaign would be on a monthly cost.
Just kind of easiest way to present this. Um,
so we would be doing everything that I proposed over here.
The one thing that I foc took out was the LSAs. Um,
really this is about supporting you with ongoing content,
supporting you with ongoing local. That's, you know, 80% of this proposal here.
Um, and then the link consulting. So I put this in on a thousand dollars basis,
so probably like two calls a month with your, blanking on her name again,
I apologize, but just to come up with strategies to do some training,
some coaching, and, um, help her to be able to acquire links for you.
Plus we'd also provide you like some sites from our database.
So essentially you're saving a ton of money on links with this and you're also
able to do it in-house. Um, you know,
you could potentially pull that out too if you didn't want to, if this, uh,
wanted to get to a certain price range, et cetera.
But this is pretty much in the ballpark that we had spoken about,
right between like four and eight, right in the middle. Um,
and I feel like this is a scope that we're comfortable with,
that you can pass this over to us, we can take it, uh,
and still provide a very good base of consulting and communication. Back to you.
Also took out the analytics quote. We're still gonna do this.
This is like reporting goal tracking set up, et cetera. Uh,
but just to keep the price, uh, and a place that we discussed,
we're happy to just throw that in there. So if you have any questions,
let me know. If not, um,
all you have to do is accept this just via email and I'll send you over a
statement of work.
We'll get that signed just to lock it in and we can go from there. So,
looking forward to potentially working together. Talk soon.